It's hard it's very hard it's very hard to lose
es duro es muy duro es muy duro perder
a loved one like that and it's even harder to
un ser querido de esa manera y más duro
find out about it in the press but it's not the
enterarte por la prensa pero no es el
only case lots of cases that I
único caso montones de casos que yo
know of have been found out about in the press
conozco se han enterado por la prensa
for example walfran his brother dies his
por ejemplo walfran que muere el hermano
sister in law dies and the two
muere la cuñada y mueren los dos
nephews die here in Pio They live in
sobrinos aquí en Pio Ellos viven en
Brazil he is at his house one morning
Brasil él está en su casa en una mañana
and he calls his brother in law and says walfran
y lo Llama a su cuñado le dice walfran
come here it's been a month since the brother had been
vente llevaban un mes que el hermano no
in touch with them he didn't
se ponía en contacto con ellos no lo
call him on the phone it seemed strange to them
llamaba por teléfono les parecía raro
because also he had the tickets
porque Además él tenía los billetes
bought to come in September to his
comprados para venir en septiembre a su
house to his brother's house he was going to
casa a la casa del hermano se iba a
come to Europe he hasn't
venir para Europa lleva un mes sin sin
spoken to them for a month now pissed off because it's
hablar con ellos ya porque es
clear that my brother doesn't get in
Claro que mi hermano ya no se pone en
touch with us well anyway brother in law
contacto con nosotros bueno pores cuñado
in the morning I'll call him tomorrow he says hey
por la mañana lo llamo mañana dice Oye
well Fran come here to the house come to the
bueno Fran vente aquí a cas ven un
garage for a moment my brother in law had
momentito a la cochera el cuñado tenía
a limia car business I want to
un negocio de limia coche que te quiero
show you something like he played
enseñar una cosa como era jugado de
professional soccer he thought it was hab
fútbol profesional pensó que era hab
map to play soccer in the morning but
mapa jugar fútbol por la mañana pero
when he gets there his brother in law says here and  He
cuando llega allí el cuñado dice toma y
leaves a newspaper from Brazil and says look what it
le deja un periódico de Brasil dice mira
says here and it says in the newspaper
lo que pone aquí y pone en el periódico
found in Spain Brazilian family
encontrada en España familia brasileña
dead murdered of course what happens at that
muerta asesinada claro qué pasa en ese
moment it didn't say names there was no photo
momento no ponía nombres no había foto
of the house in the newspaper but of course I have
de la casa en el periódico pero claro yo
n't spoken to my family for a month
llevo un mes sin hablar con mi familia
automatically I know it's them he says I
automáticamente sé que son ellos dice yo
get in the car crying like a
cojo el coche llorando como una
Magdalene my world was ending I get
Magdalena Ya mi mundo se acababa llego a
home
mi casa